milkandmore.co.uk 2015-12-29

# milk&more Privacy Policy | Milk delivery service

### 1\. About Us

**milk &more** is committed to preserving the privacy of all visitors to [www.milkandmore.co.uk](http://www.milkandmore.co.uk/)

Please read the following privacy policy to understand how we use and protect the personal information that you provide to us when you use this website. By entering your personal information in the **milk &more** website you accept that we may retain your information and it may be held by **milk &more** and any third party company which processes it on our behalf.

We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure you are happy with any change. This Privacy Policy was most recently updated on 09 May 2012. 

If you have any questions about this policy or do not agree with it, please contact [datacontroller@dairycrest.co.uk](mailto:datacontroller@dairycrest.co.uk) before using this website

### 2\. Information that we collect from you

When you visit this website we may collect the following information:

  * your name and contact information, delivery address, email address and date of birth;
  * billing information, transaction and payment details; and
  * information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experiences with our products and contact preferences in order to provide you with further correspondence about our goods and services.

We may collect information about your use of our website, including by way of requesting information from you on a voluntary basis or by the use of third party software to capture information about your visit. This is designed to help us improve the quality of our service.

We may collect sensitive personal data (as defined under the Data Protection Act 1998) from you if you order a specialist product, for example, milk products which are gluten free or suitable for people with a lactose intolerance. However, we do not collect any information about any underlying health issue or symptoms. By ordering these sorts of specialist products you are agreeing that we may use this information to process your order.

### 3\. Use of your information

All information collected via our website is used to operate and improve the service we offer you and in particular for the following purposes:

  * to process orders, payments and refunds;
  * for internal record keeping;
  * to follow up if you have purchased goods from our website as part of our customer care procedures;
  * to assess your request for the delivery of goods from us where we may make enquiries about you including searching records held by credit reference agencies or fraud prevention schemes;
  * to enable our debt collection agency to collect payment from you should that be necessary;
  * to monitor and improve the **milk &more** website, our goods and services;
  * to conduct market research including statistical analysis of customer behaviour; and
  * to enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf.
  * to validate and and verify your identity with Experian.
  * to check your direct debit details are correct using personal details(account name & address info) with Experian.

### 4\. Direct Marketing

We would like to provide you with information about new products, promotions, special offers and other information which we think you may find interesting. We may also contact you to take part in market research to help us improve our service. We may send you such information by mail, leaflets, telephone or email. It is your choice whether to opt in to this kind of communication at the time of registration and you are able to change your preference at any time via "My account".

### 5\. Disclosure of your information

The information you provide to us may be given to the staff working within **milk &more** and third parties who act for us for the purposes set out in this policy (such as processing payments through a secure network) or for other purposes approved by you unless you tell us that you do not wish this to happen. Those third parties process information, handle competitions and promotions and provide support services on our behalf.

We will not transfer, disclose, sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties other than those mentioned above, unless we have your permission or are required by law. The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may be processed by third parties operating outside the EEA who work for us for the purposes set out in this policy. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

### 6\. Security and data retention 

We employ security measures to protect your information from access by unauthorised persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss destruction and damage. We will retain your information for as long as the law requires.

### 7\. Accessing and updating

You may request details of personal information, which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee may be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please contact [datacontroller@dairycrest.co.uk](mailto:datacontroller@dairycrest.co.uk).

If you think any information we have about you is incorrect or incomplete, please update via "My account" as soon as possible.

### 8\. Linking 

We may link to other websites, which are not within our control. Once you have left our website, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### 9\. Cookies 

milk&more uses cookies for certain features & functions of our website. Cookies are files that store information on your hard drive or browser to ensure that our site works correctly to give you the best possible experience. They make it easier for you to maintain your preferences on the website, and by seeing how you use the website, we can tailor the website around your preferences and measure usability of the website. Below is a list of the cookies we use on milkandmore.co.uk and what they are used for.

**Cookie Name** | **What we use it for**  
---|---  
**XXDCDepotId** | To check your postcode during registration to find your nearest delivery depot.  
**XXDCMilkMan** | To check your postcode, telling you who your milkman will be. This information is displayed when you log into your account online and is automatically updated should your milkman change.  
**XXDCRoundId** | To assign your account to the nearest depot & milkman with a 'Round ID number' so we can make deliveries to you and monitor the level of service you receive.  
**XXDCDeliveryPattern** | To be able to inform you on which days your milkman will deliver. You can view this information by logging into your account. This will automatically update if your milkman ever changes.  
**backLinkURL** | To allow you to navigate around the milk&more website, going back to previous pages without losing the contents of your shopping basket.  
**holidayPage** | To enable the holiday feature to suspend your orders while you are away.  
**ReferaFriend** | To let you use our Refer A Friend offer by checking your account and generating a unique promotional code for you to share with friends & family to get you both money off your shopping. You can find out more about our Refer a Friend offer here.  
**RequestCtx.CART_ID** | To store the items you have put into your shopping basket by assigning it with a unique ID number linked to your milk&more account. If you do not complete your shopping for any reason, the items will stay in your shopping basket until you come back to the milk&more website and either confirm, update or delete the order. You will not receive a delivery of items in your shopping basket until you have confirmed your order.  
**amendVarAmt** | To check and update the value of your orders when you make changes.  
**PayDiff** | To check your account credit limit against the value of your shopping basket to see whether you need to make a one-off payment for your order.  
**updStr** | To store your order details for current shopping basket and regular orders.  
**virtualShop** | To see if you are browsing one of our 'Virtual' categories, found at the bottom of the Shop page, and show you the products associated with the part of the shop you are browsing.  
**XXDCviewFlag** | To see if you are logged into your account, so that the site can display your account information and let you shop for products.  
**highlightValue** | To control the appearanceof the left hand menu to highlight which section you are currently browsing.  
  
**3rd Party Cookies**

**Cookie Name** | **What we use it for**  
---|---  
**SIVISITOR** | SIVISITOR provides milk&more with secure specialist tracking software to allow us to analyse how our customers interact with our site - from which promotions and products are most (or least) popular, to what operating system, web browser and even screen size you use to visit our site.   
This information helps us to make improvements to the shopping experience, the products and offers available and how we communicate with you so that you get the best from milk&more.   
The data gathered by the software is only available to the appropriate teams at ‘SIVISITOR’ and milk&more and never shows or stores any personal or confidential information.  
**Google** | milk&more uses Google's analytics tools as an additional support tool for SIVISITOR. The data gathered is very similar, stored securely by Google and only available to the appropriate team in milk&more.  
**Digital Window** | Digital Window is used to track visitors to the milk&more website from our affiliates websites. The cookie is set when you click on an advert from milk&more shown on one of our affiliates websites. The cookie stores information such as the time, date, and originating affiliate source.   
More information on Digital Window's own Privacy Policy can be found [here](http://www.digitalwindow.com/privacy/awin1.html)  
**Cadreon** | Cadreon software advertises milk&more products and offers to new customers in key online locations and reports on the popularity of those adverts to ensure that we are only showing you information you might be interested in.  
  
milk&more does not use any other third party cookies to store or share your personal information. Our Refer a Friend offer provides the facility to share your unique offer code on your Facebook or Twitter account. Any cookies used by these websites are not controlled by milk&more so we suggest that you check these websites for more information on using and managing their cookies.

**Facebook privacy policy:  
**<http://www.facebook.com/policy.php>

Twitter privacy policy:   
<https://twitter.com/privacy>

**Managing Cookies**

None of the cookies on milk&more are used to store financial information, or information that could be used to identify you but are essential to ensure that the site works as it should - such as checking to see that you are logged in and can place an order.

You can, should you choose, disable the cookies from your browser and delete all cookies currently stored on your computer. On Microsoft Internet Explorer, this can be done by selecting "Tools/Internet Options" and reviewing your privacy settings or selecting "delete cookies". This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. You can find out how to do this for your particular browser by clicking "help" on your browser's menu.

**All this talk of cookies...**

Whilst milk&more doesn't actually sell real cookies, we do sell a wide range of biscuits and cakes as well as crisps and other snacks. Why not browse the shop for a bit of biscuity inspiration?

### 10\. Contact us 

All comments, queries or requests relating to our use of your information are welcomed and should be addressed to the [datacontroller@dairycrest.co.uk](mailto:datacontroller@dairycrest.co.uk). 

If you have any feedback about a **milk &more** product you have bought, please contact us by phone or via your **milk &more** account.

**milk &more** is owned and operated by Müller UK & Ireland Group LLP, trading as **milk &more**, a private limited partnership registered in England and our partnership number is OC384928 ("Müller UK & Ireland Group LLP"). The registered office address of Müller UK & Ireland Group LLP is Tern Valley Business Park, Shrewsbury Road, Market Drayton, Shropshire, TF9 3SQ. Our VAT number is GB687909563.
